chinaspringtour.com 2017-06-10

# Spring Privacy Policy —Springairlines

**  
1\. Scope**  
The Privacy Policy will apply to all customers using Spring Group services, products and websites.

**2\. Information Collection**  
(1) Direct Collection。  
Personal information is not mandatory to access and surf Spring websites but on some pages we may ask you to enter personal information in order to allow us to provide you products and services according to your requirements or transaction.  
The personal information we collect about you may include but is not limited to the following:  
∷Contact information (such as your name, email address, telephone number or address);  
∷Personal information (such as Identity card number, passport number, date of birth);  
∷Your preferences of receiving promotional email;  
∷Financial information, including credit card or bank account details;  
∷Information helping us determine the best products and services to meet your needs and expectations;  
∷Event registration information;   
∷Your overall feedback regarding the content of our website, products and services.  
You are not required to provide any information, but if we do not have such information we may not be able to respond to your request, provide you products or services, or complete transactions.  
(2) Automatic Collection  
Spring may collect information about your visit to our sites, including pages you are browsing, amount of data transferred, links clicked and information accessed, as well as any other operations performed within this website.   
We will use your information to provide and personalize our services.   
Cookies. Cookies enable Spring Airlines to provide features such as remembering aspects of your previous searches within our websites. They are also used in email messages you have agreed to receive and within our website to study how our customers use the website and how to improve its design and content. By clicking on an email link , you may set a cookie. 

**3\. Purpose of collecting personal information**  
Personal information obtained from customers will be used for the following purposes:  
(1)Reservations, ticket sales, check-in, airport services, and in-flight services with regard to air transport services  
(2)Sales of insurance or, if necessary, any other services provided by Spring, its authorized agent or service provider.  
(3)Wet lease, code share, intermodal transportation.  
(4)Guidance, provision, and management of other services and products offered by Spring.  
(5)All operations incidental or related to the above[1]-[4].  
(6)Questionnaires concerning products and services, etc. offered by Spring.  
(7)To conduct sales analysis, investigations and researches; to develop new services and products.  
(8)Notification of services and products offered by Spring.  
(9)Providing various information on services, products, events and campaigns of Spring's parent companies, subsidiaries and partner companies.  
(10)Responses to enquiries and requests.

**4\. Managing personal information**   
Spring Airlines commits itself to appropriately manage and protect customers' personal information, according to the strictest standards and to take the utmost care to prevent leaks, loss, or alterations.  
The user creates his/ her own ID and password to log-in to the website. The user is responsible for all actions taken under this user ID, including any actions of others who have been authorized to use your user ID (possibly by you yourself).  
The ID user can at any time unsubscribe emails and choose not to receive products and services offers any longer. 

**5\. Disclosure to a third party**  
Spring will not disclose or provide personal customer information to any third party except under the following circumstances or for the following purposes. Please note that provision of information to data sharing partners and business entrusted companies is not deemed to constitute disclosure or provision to a third party.  
Spring may disclose or provide personal customer information to any third party if:  
(1)Customer consent has been obtained.  
(2)Disclosure or provision is required by laws or regulations.  
(3)Disclosure is required to protect human life, health, or property in cases where obtaining customer consent is difficult.  
(4)Disclosure is required to cooperate with the public affairs of national or local governments, and when obtaining customer consent is likely to hinder the administration of public affairs.

**6\. Business entrustment**  
From time to time, Spring may entrust its business operations to third parties to which personal information may also be disclosed to the extent required. In these cases, we will implement all appropriate measures with such third parties to safeguard the confidentiality of customers’ data, including establishing agreements to handle such personal information.

**7\. Links to Third Party Websites**  
Spring’s websites contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each site that collects information from you. Spring’s Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Spring on its own website.

**8\. Application and modification of the Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy explains how Spring handles customers’ personal information. Use of Spring products and services by a customer is deemed to be fully aware of and understanding of and consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is subject to revision by Spring at any time and changes will be posted on this page.
